Contact

doreen.c.gonzales@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/doreengonzales-mba-msn-rnbc-7512a996 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Operations Management Leadership Healthcare Management

Languages

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Nursing Informatics Board Certified

Doreen Gonzales, MBA, MSN, RN-BC

Chief Operating Officer/Chief Nursing Officer at ZAZEN Group Katy, Texas

Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Operations Management, Healthcare Informatics, Workflow Redesign, Customer Service, and Project Management. Strong quality assurance professional with a Master's Degree focused in Informatics from Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center and Business Administration from Western Governors University..

Experience

ZAZEN Surgery Center, Zazen Medical Group, Zazen Wellness Chief Operating Officer/Chief Nursing Officer August 2019 - Present (10 months)

Katy, Texas

Zazen Surgery Center, Zazen Medical Group, Zazen Spa & Wellness

Zazen Surgery Center
Chief Nursing Officer
October 2018 - August 2019 (11 months)

HCA Gulf Coast Division 2 years 7 months

Interim Manager of Nursing Administration June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months)

Emergency Department Nurse Manager February 2016 - June 2018 (2 years 5 months)

Cypress Fairbanks Medical Center Hospital 5 years 4 months

Quality Assurance Coordinator March 2015 - June 2018 (3 years 4 months)

Page 1 of 2

Informatics RN Specialist March 2013 - June 2018 (5 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Tenet Healthcare
Emergency Room RN
November 2007 - March 2015 (7 years 5 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Memorial Hermann Health System ER and Pediatric Transport RN September 1998 - November 2007 (9 years 3 months)

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration, Healthcare Management · (2018 - 2019)

Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center Master of Science in Nursing , Informatics · (2015 - 2016)

Central Philippine University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1993 - 1997)